howmanyofme.com 2019-12-13

# How Many of Me - Privacy Policy

Last changed: Feb 28, 2010

Q: What kind of information is collected?

A: The web site asks that users enter first and last names to discover how common or uncommon they are. The user may enter their own name, or anyone else's name. For statistical purposes we track the number of searches and what names were searched for by an individual user. A typical user will search a number of different names (themselves, friends, family, celebrities) and determining which search was their name would be difficult. However, it is conceivable that a first and last name of a user could be discovered.

The web site also allows users to enter their e-mail address for the purpose of notifying users of new features of this web site, or new web sites created by the operator of this site.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

Q: With whom do you share your data?

A: We do not share search data of individual users or e-mail addresses with anyone, nor do we intend to start.

We do allow users to look at statistics based on the aggregate of all searches. Information such as the most popular name searched for by all users is available. There is no way to single out the information of one particular user from this data.

Q: How long do you retain data?

A: Raw log files, including such data as IP address, operating system, browser type, as well as some information are kept for a 7 day period, at the end of which they are aggregated into a format that makes discovering any personally identifiable information very difficult, if not impossible.

The search log including individual searches is processed approximately weekly. During processing data connecting individual users to a particular search is removed.

Q: Is this the final version of your privacy policy?

A: Probably not. Like most things on this site, our privacy policy is a work in progress. We will very likely revise the privacy policy at some point. Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted here. We do not, however, expect any changes in the core values of this privacy policy.
